http://www.roqlarue.com/privacy-statement

Privacy Statement
PRIVACY STATEMENTAcceptance of TermsRoq La Rue Gallery respects your right to privacy. By accessing or using this web site, you agree to this Privacy Statement as part of the Conditions of Use, without limitation.Your InformationYou can visit this web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. We collect personal information in connection with any order you submit under this web site to fulfill your order. If you provide us with your personal Information, you consent to the transfer and storage of your personal information on our servers. You will have the option to unsubscribe from any mailing list from Roq La Rue Gallery at any time.Other Information CollectedIf you access and browse this web site, Roq La Rue Gallery will automatically collect and store standard information collected by all web server software such as:the Internet Protocol (IP) address and domain name used (but not the email address);the type of browser and operating system you used;the date and time you visited the web site;the web pages or services you accessed at the web site; orthe web site you visited prior to coming to this web site (Note: this is done solely to determine how visitors get to this web site, i.e., from a search engine, from a link on another site, etc.).The above information may be used to diagnose problems with Roq La Rue Gallery’s server, to administer the web site and to otherwise provide services to you.Protection of Your InformationRoq La Rue Gallery will not sell or rent your information to any third party for marketing purposes. Roq La Rue Gallery will store your information in a secure operating environment that is not available for public access, however, Roq La Rue Gallery cannot guarantee complete security. Only Roq La Rue Gallery employees, consultants, agents or third party service providers with a need to know will have access to your information in order to perform services on behalf of Roq La Rue Gallery. Roq La Rue Gallery will not store your credit card information needed for financial transactions as purchases will be made through Google Checkout, or any other company designated and authorized by Roq La Rue Gallery for financial transactions.Right to Release InformationRoq La Rue Gallery shall have the right to release any information if required to do so by law or if Roq La Rue Gallery, in good faith, believes that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to any subpoenas, court orders, law enforcement officers, or other legal entity or process. Roq La Rue Gallery shall also have the right to release any information in order to respond to any claims of infringement by the content posted on the web site, to enforce Roq La Rue Gallery’s Conditions of Use, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Roq La Rue Gallery, its users or the public. In addition, if Roq La Rue Gallery goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, or consolidation, or undertakes to sell a portion of its assets, your information will in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.
